Nicholas Weber

Web Developer

nikkoweber@live.com · (763)-218-5996

Professional Summary

More than four years of experience as both a designer and developer of corporate websites. Have numerous achievements under my belt, including the complete design and development of a corporate website (100+ pages including an eCommerce system) from scratch. Experience with both traditional web markup and content management systems; able to adaptably use both with proficiency.

Experience

Web Developer Intern

Lube-Tech, Golden Valley, MN / Jan 2016 - Feb 2020

- Designed the company website
- Developed the company website in Angular
- Designed and implemented the UI for the eCommerce system
- Made modifications and additions to the website over time

Web Developer

TravelNet Solutions, Cottage Grove, MN / Feb 2020 - Mar 2020

- Developed web content in the WordPress theme Avada
- Implemented web content for various clients
- Created modifications to the existing web content

Education

Capella University (2018-2019)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Minor: Web Application Development

Professional Skills

- Front-end web development
- User experience design
- Angular
- JavaScript
- Image manipulation
- Prototyping
- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- WordPress

References available upon request Portfolio available at nikkoweber.com